donbest.com 2010-02-20

# Privacy Statement - Customers | DonBest

**DON BEST SPORTS IS COMMITTED TO YOUR PRIVACY**

This website is managed by SBR Netmarketing and Consulting S.A. for Don Best Sports (hereinafter both entities will collectively be referred to as “us, we, our”).  

We value your patronage and respect your privacy rights. As part of the normal operation of our services, we collect and, in some cases, may disclose information about you. We have created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our web site, why we collect it, and how it is used. This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to us and is maintained electronically, whether you provide the information through our website located at www.donbest.com (the "Site"), or through other means. Additionally, this Privacy Policy applies to any Personal Information (defined below) obtained from your use of the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that you may provide to third parties; for example, other sites linked to this Site. You should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies.  
This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms of Use found at www.donbest.com. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. If you believe we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy or if you have any other questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [webmaster@donbest.com](mailto:webmaster%40donbest.com).  

**SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT CHILDREN**  

This Site is targeted primarily for use by adults. We do not currently market to or create special areas for use by children. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect age identifying information, nor do we knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 years. However, we hereby advise all visitors to our site under the age of 13 not to disclose or provide any Personal Information on our website. In the event that we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, in accordance with the United States Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (please see the Federal Trade Commission's website at [www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy](http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy "www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy") for more information about this Act), we will delete the child's Personal Information from our files to the extent technologically possible.  

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU AND WHY?**  
We collect and maintain a variety of Personal Information about you to enable us to provide you with the best service. "Personal Information" is information about you by which you may be identified. We currently collect Personal Information through e-mail and the various online inquiry forms on the Site. The Personal Information we collect and maintain about you includes:

  * your name, your phone number and address (street and e-mail) 
  * information about your preferences regarding sports and entertainment

We only collect Personal Information that you voluntarily provide to us or voluntarily provide to our Partners (defined below) who share that information with us. We also use your Personal Information for other things that may include, but are not limited to, the following: 

  * **_Contacting You_**

We use your Personal Information to communicate with you in the event we have any questions with regard to your online inquiry. We may also contact you to tell you about products and services provided by our Partners, other affiliates and other third-party organizations.

  * **_Interactions_**

Each time you interact with our Site, the details of your interaction are collected and retained. 

  * **_Correspondence_**

We intend to retain any correspondence, including facsimiles, mail and e-mails, set to us. We also may retain correspondence such as customer service e-mails from us to you. We may delete such records over time. 

  * **_Use of IP Address_**

IP addresses are numbers that are automatically assigned to your computer, and, if associated with other individually identifiable information, could be considered personal information. Your user IP address information is used only for our internal tracking purposes. 

  * **_Use of Cookies_**

Cookies are a standard technology used by commercial web services to store small pieces of information on your hard drive by sending a small string of text to your browser. They make your use of this Site more pleasing and efficient by "personalizing" your Site experience and gathering Site statistical data, such as which parts of the Site you have previously visited, what material you downloaded, your Internet provider's domain name and country, and the addresses of websites you visited immediately before and after our Site. They enable us to tailor the information you receive and to assist our Partners or other third party organizations with whom we have strategic alliances by identifying you as our customer or Site user. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, unless you have configured yours not to accept them. Typically, we do not use cookies, however, if we so chose to use cookies in order for us to provide you with services on our Site, your browser must accept cookies, as they are essential for site administration and security. We do not use cookies either to collect individually identifiable information or to collect non-individually identifiable information using a cookie that is combined with a personal identifier.

  * **_Provision of Personal Information to Third Parties_**

It should be clearly understood that the contact coordinates relating to each person which accesses our (or any of our affiliates') websites or purchases any of our (or any of our affiliates') services and which we access to their respective contact coordinates may be provided to third parties (in exchange for compensation or otherwise) for an indefinite period of time without any compensation being payable to the subject person. Such third parties may be using this personal information to contact you to solicit, advertise or market their products and/or services to you.   
Should you have any questions, concerns or disagree with the possible provision of your personal information in the manner that is described herein, please contact our Chief Privacy Officer ("CPO") at the contact coordinates noted below.  

**WHAT GENERAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU AND WHY?**

"General Information" is information about you or your activities on our Site that do not identify you personally. When you use the Internet, your web browser or software may communicate certain information to the host website you visit. This information may include the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, the capabilities and features of your computer, you geographic location, and your movement and activity within a particular website. We collect the same information on our Site. We use this General Information to generate statistics about visitors to our Site.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

The information we collect is used to (i) to respond to your inquiries; (ii) provide customer services and resolve any complaints; (iii) improve the Site and service and resolve any technical problems; (iv) communicate with you concerning the services offered on the Site by us or any of our Partners; (v) cross-reference with other Personal Information that we have acquired about you or may acquire about you through other sources; (vi) create aggregate data; (vii) ensure compliance with the Site Terms of Use; and (viii) comply with any applicable laws and regulations. We may provide your information to government officials and agencies as required by law, and Partners as part of business operations, transaction processing, and marketing efforts, as identified below. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Partner" shall mean any person or entity with whom we enter into any kind of business transaction who is under an obligation to us to use reasonable care to keep Personal Information confidential.

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any Personal Information obtained by us through this Site or from our Partners about you, without your consent. We may disclose Personal Information (i) to companies that help process the transactions you request, in order to protect your transactions from fraud and verify your identity; (ii) that we in good faith believe is necessary or appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud, intellectual property infringements or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability, or to conduct investigations of violations of the Site Terms of Use; (iii) when required by law or to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; (iv) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of governmental authorities (including, without limitation, requests from the governmental agency authorities to view your Personal Information); (v) to protect and defend us, our subsidiaries and affiliates and any of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors and partners, in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; (vi) to prevent imminent physical harm; (vii) to share aggregated statistical or demographic data with our affiliates, business partners or for public relations (this aggregated information is not tied to Personal Information); (viii) to provide data, including Personal Information about you, with our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries and Partners; (ix) to sell or otherwise provide to third parties in the event of a bankruptcy or liquidation; and (x) to sell or otherwise provide to third parties in the event of a future merger or acquisition by another company. In the event we merge or are acquired by another company, the successor company will have access to your Personal Information in order to continue to provide services, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy unless and until it is amended as described in the subsection labeled "Changes to this Privacy Policy" below.

**HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. Although no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented on our Site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

**HOW LONG WE KEEP USER INFORMATION**

We generally keep user data on our server or in our archives for as long as we reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, we may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely. Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within our direct control. Please note that we have greater control over recently collected data than over archived data. Once data is removed from the system and archived, it may not be feasible to accommodate specific requests. In those cases, our general data retention policy applies.

**PERSONAL CHOICE IN THE DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with our Partners for marketing purposes, or if you do not want to receive certain communications and offers from us you can "opt out" of such sharing, communications by contacting us via email at [webmaster@donbest.com](mailto:webmaster%40donbest.com), or write us at:  
Don Best Sports  
1311 Howe Street, Suite 401  
Vancouver, British Columbia V6Z 2P3  
If you believe that any Personal Information collected by us about you is not correct or has changed, please send an e-mail message to [webmaster@donbest.com](mailto:webmaster%40donbest.com) explaining the correction or change and providing any relevant confirmation or reference number.

**DISCLOSURE OF PRIVACY PROVISIONS SPECIFIC TO CANADIAN RESIDENTS**

We are committed to operating pursuant to applicable Laws and respecting the privacy of individuals. We recognize the rights of the people with whom we do business and of our employees concerning the appropriate management and protection of any personal information, which we receive or which is provided to us.

With respect to the collection, storage, use and retention of your personal information, we operate pursuant to the following Privacy Management Guideline:

**Collection** : We collect personal information about individuals (clients, customers, employees, etc.) in order to better manage its business. In appropriate circumstances, we will make all reasonable efforts to fully inform such individuals about the planned use/disclosure. We will limit the collection and use of personal information to that required for valid business purposes or to comply with applicable legislation.

**Accuracy** : We will make every reasonable effort to ensure that the personal information it collects and uses is accurate and complete. Upon written request to our CPO, individuals will have the opportunity to review and correct their personal information and we will modify the information required.

**Storage** : We will store personal information using hard copy and/or electronic means in such a way as to use its commercially reasonable best efforts to prevent unauthorized collection, access, use, disclosure, or disposal of the personal information.

**Retention** : From time to time, we will establish a retention period for all personal information collected. This period may be related to legislated obligations.

**Disclosure** : Except as provided herein, we will not disclose personal information unnecessarily to employees or any third party, unless the affected individual consents.

**Access** : We promote an individual's right and access to personal information about themselves and our CPO will provide access to such information upon request. Access will be provided according to an established procedure, which is in place from time to time. Please note that access to a record may be subject to the payment of any fee required, according to applicable our policy.

**Care** : In addition to the care that we take directly, we also work with the third parties that lease the personal information and all of our partner organizations that may, at some point, handle personal information gathered by us in the course of their relationship with, and service to, us to ensure they also use their commercially reasonable best efforts to meet these Guidelines and our standards of privacy, confidentiality, and security.

**Management** : All employees and third-party staff who in any way handle or manage personal information have been made aware of this Privacy Management Plan and the supporting procedures. Our CPO: For further information concerning our privacy policy, please contact:

**Chief Privacy Officer**  
Subject: Privacy Policy Inquiry  
or write the CPO at  
Don Best Sports  
1311 Howe Street, Suite 401  
Vancouver, British Columbia V6Z 2P3  
Attention: Chief Privacy Officer

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

By using this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. When this Privacy Policy is changed, modified or amended, the revised Privacy Policy will be posted on this Site. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to Personal Information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy. It is your responsibility to periodically check and review our Privacy Policy for changes.

**IF YOU HAVE A PRIVACY QUESTION**

If you have a privacy question about this Site, please email: Customer Service at [webmaster@donbest.com](mailto:webmaster%40donbest.com)

Or write to:

Customer Service  
Don Best Sports  
1311 Howe Street, Suite 401  
Vancouver, British Columbia V6Z 2P3

**DATE LAST MODIFIED: September 30, 2009**

? Big Stick Media Corporation. All Rights Reserved.

Activities offered by advertising links to other sites may be deemed an illegal activity in certain jurisdictions. Viewers are specifically warned that they should inquire into the legality of participating in any games and/or activities offered by such other sites. The owner of this website assumes no responsibility for the actions by and makes no representation or endorsement of any of these games and/or activities offered by the advertiser. As a condition of viewing this website viewers agree to hold the owner of this website harmless from any claims arising from the viewer's participation in any of the games and/or activities offered by the advertiser.

US CITIZENS PLEASE NOTE: The information contained at this site is for news and entertainment purposes only. Any use of this information in violation of any federal, state, provincial or local law is prohibited. ? Big Stick Media Corporation
